http://www.brucefuneralhome.com/privacy-policy

Funeral Services
What is a Funeral?
Privacy Policy
At our funeral home, we understand that the privacy of our visitors and the knowledge of our use of information collected from each visitor is important in our activities. Please feel free to read our privacy policy and we encourage you to contact our firm about any of the information located below if you need further assistance.Contact Information: Bruce Funeral Home, Inc.106 South CenterPO Box 192Gardner KS US66030 Phone: 913-856-7111 Email Address:  bfhomeinc1@aol.com
Your IP Address We collect the IP Address and Domain Name that is used when surfing our web site. We use this information for Site Traffic Statistics and analysis. We also receive your IP Address when you complete a search or purchase on our site in order to help our firm better recognize what is being searched by our visitors. All IP Addresses and Domain Names are kept with the utmost confidentiality. Use of Cookies A cookie is used by our funeral home only when there is persistent data that is required to use the Web Site, ie. Administration Mode, and when an E-Commerce order form is being completed. For general viewing of pages, there is no use of cookies.When a user wishes to purchase product(s) they will be asked to complete an online form. When a user completes a section of the form and clicks on the "Next" button, not only does the form progress to the Next page but a cookie is created on the visitor's computer with the information that they just completed. The purpose of the shopping basket cookie is to remember your information so that if you leave or get disconnected and come back to the order form our server will be able to complete the sections of the order form for you including product selected. E-Commerce Module To ensure that all data remains private and secure, we exclusively use secure network connections. These secure network connections are the only way that credit card and other personal information is handled. Any and all sensitive authorization data, including but not limited to credit card information is never stored by FrontRunner Professional, any employee therein or FrontRunner Professional. All payment details are securely transmitted by third party processors on secure networks connections. If you have any questions please contact accountingdept@frontrunner360.com. Questions & Comments If you have questions, comments or concerns with either the way we use the information that is collected from your web browser or our privacy policy, please feel free to contact our firm.
913-856-7111
Bruce Funeral Home, Inc.
106 South Center
PO Box 192
Gardner, KS
66030
Fax:
913-884-7009
Email:
Email:
bfhomeinc1@aol.com
Admin|Obittree|Privacy Policy|Terms of Use|Sitemap| Obituary Directory
|Powered by FrontRunner Professional
Share by:
